Sorry, we have uh the newest cowboy on
the line.
>> Oh, let's party.
>> Let's talk to Jan Bara before we go to
break on the fan real quickly. Jan,
congratulations on this moment. Welcome
to Dallas. What's going through your
head right now?
>> Uh, no, I'm feeling excited. Uh, I feel
like I had a good good top 30 visit with
him. Uh, my mother a big fan. So, I feel
like this was just it was meant to be
almost.
>> That's true. You are a local product in
that, but what's it mean to be drafted
by the the Cowboys in this moment?
What's going through your head?
>> I don't know. I think it feel great, but
I mean it's going through my head. I'm
ready to work. So, I can't wait to get
out there, put the pads on, and start
practicing.
>> Jan, congrats. Congrats. When you were
meeting with uh Dallas and the coaches
on defense, did they think of you as
more of a edge guy or more as offball
linebacker? 50-50 split. What do you
think?
>> Uh, we talked about both to be honest. I
got to meet with the outside backing
coach and the inside backers coach just
just to talk ball and see how I see
stuff. Uh going over my inside backer
tape and outside backers tape. Uh but to
me I think they see me as like a guy
that can play both.
>> We have Jan Burum on the line. Newest
Dallas Cowboy with the pick at 92. We
have to say goodbye to our listeners on
1053. The fan will continue on on
dallascowboys.com. If you're watching on
the stream, it'll be uninterrupted. Be
sure to join us. DallasCowboys.com.
We'll see you tomorrow, 10 a.m. Central
time on the Dallas Cowboys Radio Network
and on dallascowboys.com.
>> All right, Jan, you're still there,
right?
>> Yes, sir, man.
>> All right, so I just want to make sure
we're going to continue the interview
here. Appreciate you sticking around.
This is a a a draft where Dallas has
been defensive heavy already. How much
do you know about what you're coming
into and the situation that's at hand
here in Dallas?
>> I mean, I pretty much know what I'm
coming into. I seen they just got with
Shawn Gary, uh, Malik Lawrence in this
draft. So, uh, I feel like this is going
to be a deep deep room and it's going to
be fun.
>> J Sean, congratulations on getting
drafted. Excited to have you here. I'm
curious, you know, there's obviously a
lot of talk about what you're able to
do, you know, physically on the football
field, but there there's also a lot of
talk whenever people mention you about
just your motor and your intensity and
your play style. How important is that
aspect of your game just to, you know,
the relentless pursuit and that motor
running hot?
I mean, I feel like that's that's a
great thing because that's really
something you can't coach. So, I feel
like stuff like that, like your motor
and your pursuit to the ball and just
your want, I feel like that's something
that every coach want their team. So, I
feel like that's that's great.
>> Yeah. I I've described you as a havoc
type of player. How would you describe
yourself as a football player for Cowboy
fans that haven't been able to watch you
yet?
>> Oh, yeah. I like that word. I mean, I'm
trying to I'm trying to blow stuff up.
Uh cause havoc like you say and I'm
trying to cause problems for the
offense.
J Sean, is it uh is it going to be tough
at all to share your rookie class with
an Ohio State Buckeye?
>> No, I don't think so. We can make some
work. It's probably going to be a little
trash talk, but it's all right.
>> That's the best answer you could have
given. I love that. We got the chance to
meet Caleb DS today. We're going to get
a chance to meet you very, very soon.
What would you say Cowboys fans are
getting off the field with with J Sean?
>> I mean, I feel like they got a guy
that's not going to get any trouble. uh
just going to lead by the right way on
and off the field pretty much and uh I'm
going to represent that star the right
way.
>> What are some of the things you like to
do?
>> Uh me I like to watch movies uh hang
with my family. Uh just that's probably
the most part. But I'm a TV show guy. I
like to be in the house, watch shows,
movies with my family, stuff like that.
>> All right. What show are you watching
right now?
>> Oh, I just finished Pey Blinders. You
seen that?
>> Nice.
>> That's a good one.
>> Were you able to watch it without
subtitles? Could you understand all
their accents?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it took me a little
like for the first two episodes. I had I
had to fill him out. I had to hear me. I
had to fill him out for the first two
episodes, but we got there.
>> Hey, he got there. That's
>> I never did. I never did.
>> That's what he's trying to do here. I
can't wait. How was the the process
leading up to this point in talking with
Christian Parker? Uh who were some of
the the individuals that really uh had
their uh their eyes on you on the
Cowboys side?
>> I mean, for sure, Coach Parker. And
definitely when I first got to meet him,
it was like it was like we kind of had a
kind of had a match already cuz we knew
a lot of the same guys coming up. Uh
he's from the Virginia area. So I feel
like it was kind of almost a connection
and he got me on the board and I feel
like that kind of that kind of helped
him with me. Just me getting on the
board, drawing up a play that they
showed me earlier and just me being able
to recite that and remember that play. I
feel like that kind of grew with him
too. So I feel like that was a good
connection. Jan, this off seasonason,
just as a pass rusher, like what's uh
what's something you uh feel like you
can work on? Was it hands? Was it
counters? Was it uh putting moves
together? What's something that you
really feel like you wanted to focus on
this offseason as a rusher?
>> Uh to me, I think it's my counters.
>> Yeah,
>> I think I can work on my counters more
just when I get to the top of the rush,
go back, or just working on different
moves, just perfecting my craft. I'm not
perfect, so I feel like it's still a lot
I can work on and get better at.
>> Hey man, shouts out to you, bro. you
went early. I was a big fan of watching
you, man. You was whooping up on
everybody. You know what I'm saying? I
just saw you as a as a pass rusher at
first and then I just watched the
Oklahoma film. I was like, "Oh, boy.
He's a offball linebacker." The whole
game just at the drop of a dime. Hey,
Jan, this week you're off the ball
linebacker. I thought that was
fantastic, bro. So, shouts out to you,
man. Glad to have you here.
>> Yes, sir.
>> There he goes, Jan. Appreciate you.
Thank you for taking some time. We'll
talk to you down the line.
>> Appreciate it. and Jan Baram 92nd
overall pick by your Dallas Cowboys in
the 2026 NFL draft.